livelife365.com 2012-03-12

# About Us/Terms/Copyright

Welcome to our website. As a visitor, you agree to comply with the following terms and conditions:

·         Our content is for general information purposes only. 

·         Neither we nor any third parties make representations or provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, reliability, timeliness, performance, availability, completeness or suitability of the information, products, services, and other materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that these may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

·         Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services, or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.

·         This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.

·         All trademarks reproduced in this website, which are not the property of or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the website.

·         Unauthorized use of this website may establish a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.

·         You may not create a link to this website from another website or document without [livelife365.com](http://livelife365.com/)’s prior written consent. 

·         Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States of America.

### Privacy policy

Livelife365.com is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. 

**What we collect**

We may ask to collect the following information:

·         Name, job title, and contact information including email address

·         Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

·         Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We use this information to understand viewer needs and provide better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

·         Internal record keeping

·         Improving our products and services

·         Periodically sending promotional email about new products, special offers, or other information we think you may find

·         Market research purposes

·         Customizing the website to your interests and preferences

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [mike@livelife365.com](mailto:mikefos365@gmail.com)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and storing information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being viewed. This helps us tailor the site to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and the data is then removed from the system. 

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other sites. We have no control over their nature, content, or availability. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. 

### Website disclaimer

The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by [livelife365.com](http://livelife365.com/) and while we endeavour to keep the information up-to-date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk. 

All information on this site is of a general nature and is furnished for your knowledge and understanding only. This information is not to be taken as medical or other health advice pertaining to your specific health and medical condition without your medical professional’s approval.

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
